<html>
<body>

<p>
this paragraph 
contains a lot of lines 
in the source code,
but the browser 
ignores it.
</p>

<p>
this paragraph
contains  a lot of spaces
in the source  code,
but the  browser 
ignores it.
</p>

<p>
the number of lines in a paragraph depends on the size of your browser window. if you resize the browser window, the number of lines in this paragraph will change.
</p>

</body>
</html>