<html>
<body bgcolor="pink"
<b><h1 align="center">About Myself</h1></b>
<img src="myself.jpg" alt="myself"
style="width:200px;height:200px">
<p>
My name is Wong Xin Huey. I am 13 years old. I am studying in 7 Theta at Sri Kuala Lumpur International School. I used to study in SJK(C) Lick Hung with Caitlyn Tiang. Now we are still in the same class. I have a harmonious family of four members including my father, my mother, my sister who is currently studying overseas and myself. We have two family pets, that is a pond of Koi fish and a poodle puppy named Tiara.
</p> 

<p>
I have several hobbies that are rather interesting. The hobby that I fancy the most is playing the piano and composing short songs. I do not really have a manuscript full of composition because I do not always write down my composition. I would just play the notes as I 'feel'the tune. There is not a single day that passes by without me playing and composing songs on the piano. My other hobby is writing stories during my free time. I have written two short stories when I was 8 years old. Now I am in the midst of writing another mystery story.
</p>

<p>
I have a best friend too. Her name is Hui Yi Xuan. We used to study in the same class in primary school. She is very pretty, intelligent, confident and helpful. She would always be there for me whenever I am in trouble or upset. However, education separated us. I am still studying in Malaysia but she won the ASEAN scholarship and is currently studying in Singapore. Although we cannot see each other face-to-face, we can still text each other using Whatsapp.
</p>

<p>
I have been to many countries in the world, such as Singapore, Thailand, Taiwan and Japan. My parents believe that travelling allows one to learn and enjoy at the same time. I am so happy that in my travels I have been exposed to the different cultures of the countries that I have visited. Of all the countries that I have visited the country that I like the most is Japan. Their local delicacies were scrumptious, the roads were free of litters and the local products were cheap and of good quality. I bought many souvenirs from Japan.
</p>

<p>
I also have a few favourite singers who compose wonderful songs like Taylor Swift, Ariana Grande and Ed Sheeran. I do enjoy some K-pop songs by some of Korean bands like Girls' Generation and F(X). Sometimes I would translate the Korean lyrics to English to understand what the singers are singing. 
</p>

<br>
</br>
<b><h1>Favourite Song</h1></b>
<b><h1 align="center">Let It Go</h1></b>
<br></br>
<b><center>Let it go, Let it go,</center></b>
<b><center>Can't hold it back any more.</center></b>		
<b><center>Let it go, let it go!</center><b>
<b><center>Turn away and slam the door.</center></b>
<b><center>I don't care what they're going to say.</center></b>

</body>
</htm>


